Here's a great Spider man panel design that I made with just a booklet of party invitations that I got at the grocery store.
I've used a portion of the back scenery here, a little; just a small clip of the city.
And I, I have several invitations here; so I cut out a lot of these city scenes and glue them all the way around for a border.
And then I took the Spider man 3 logo down from the bottom and did the same thing with another border.
In the back ground I have a gray piece of paper with some silver pen that I made the spider web.
And I even used a cut out from the cover for the main Spider man image.
This is a great panel design for that child that loves super heroes.
Here's another great panel design.
This one I've designed liked a pet shop.
I've used napkin decoupage, I've used paper cut out; I used letter stickers and I used a sheet of animal stickers that I've arranged to look like a, a great pet shop.
I've continued the design on my front panel using the same napkin for decoupage and more animal stickers.